# Jane Harrison

Passionate and hard-working systems administrator with over 10 years experience working in the arts. Looking to specialize in fields related to computer science and shift my career in this direction. Skilled in multi-tasking, problemsolving and leading a team.

303-1429 William Street Vancouver, BC V5L 4W8

jxharrison@hotmail.com 604-362-4245

# SKILLS AND PROFICIENCIES

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, Python, R
- Excel
- Customer service
- Project management
- Events
- Budget management
- Leading a team
- Presentations

# **INTERESTS**

- Kickboxing
- Running
- Chess
- Kayaking
- Theatre
- Travel
- Dogs

#### **WORK HISTORY**

### **Ticketing and CRM Manager**

Vancouver International Film Festival (VIFF) Jan 2017 - Present

- Leading an organization-wide systems infrastructure project.
- Established VIFF Connect online streaming platform to host 2020 festival online.
- Responsible for VIFF Plus loyalty program increasing revenue by 105% and members by 50% between 2020 and 2021.
- Oversee all ticketing, accreditation, customer service, website maintenance and sales projections/reporting.

## **Sponsorship Assistant**

VIFF | Aug 2016 - Dec 2016

Responsible for ensuring partners were supported during the 2016 festival, tracking partner benefits, invoicing, collecting and distributing digital assets and providing event support at galas and parties.

#### **Technical Support Representative**

Shaw Communications | Apr 2015 - Aug 2016

Provided technical support for cable and internet customers over the phone. This included troubleshooting and fixing technical issues, guiding customers on how to use their equipment, escalating complex issues and resolving complaints.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Applied Data Analytics Certificate**

BCIT | ongoing, part-time

#### **English Literature, BA**

University of Newcastle Upon Tyne, UK - 2006 1st Class Honours